<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nornir.tech</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on nornir.tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Nornir</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CNaaS-NMS</title>
      <link>/2020/03/03/cnaas-nms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/03/03/cnaas-nms/</guid>
      <description>Github Docs
Campus Network-as-a-Service - Network Management System. Software to automate management of a campus network (LAN). This is an open source software developed as part of SUNETs managed service.
Planned features:
 Zero-touch provisioning of switches Automation of common changes for campus LAN Automated procedure for firmware upgrades Multi-vendor support  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stockpiler</title>
      <link>/2020/03/03/stockpiler/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/03/03/stockpiler/</guid>
      <description>Gtihub
Stockpiler gathers network device configurations and stores them in a local Git repository.
Stockpiler utilizes Nornir, Netmiko, and GitPython for a fully self-contained backup solution, and has been tested to function on Linux, MacOS, and Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About TBD</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Nornir Github Documentation Help
Nornir is a pure Python automation framework intented to be used directly from Python. While most automation frameworks use their own Domain Specific Language (DSL) which you use to describe what you want to have done, Nornir lets you control everything from Python.
 Gornir Github Documentation Help
Gornir is a pluggable framework with inventory management to help operate collections of devices. It&amp;rsquo;s similar to nornir but in golang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsoring the project</title>
      <link>/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>Both nornir and gornir are made by the community for the community. To ensure the continuity and success of the project both collaborators and/or sponsors are welcome.
If you want to sponsor the project you can do it either as an individual using github sponsors or via your company by contacting us via email
Companies sponsoring us Individuals sponsoring us Go to github sponsors and don&amp;rsquo;t forget to thank them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/</guid>
      <description>Community Support You can find community-driven support via the following channels:
 On network to code&amp;lsquo;s slack, #nornir channel On discourse   Premium Support If you need dedicated support, help developing a feature or plugin, designing and/or architecting your solution or anything else you can reach out to us and discuss your needs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>