<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nornir.tech</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on nornir.tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Nornir</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SALTSTACK Nornir Proxy Minion introduction</title>
      <link>/2021/07/16/saltstack-nornir-proxy-minion-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/07/16/saltstack-nornir-proxy-minion-introduction/</guid>
      <description>This is a guest post by Denis Mulyalin, follow github account and twitter feed for latest updates.
 SALTSTACK Nornir Proxy Minion introduction Network Automation is a complex but interesting topic with a lot of challenges to explore and a lot to learn, defined by one of the vendors as:
 Network automation is the process of automating the configuring, managing, testing, deploying, and operating of physical and virtual devices within a network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To: Filtering Deep Dive</title>
      <link>/2021/04/19/how-to-filtering-deep-dive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/04/19/how-to-filtering-deep-dive/</guid>
      <description>This is a guest post by Daniel Teycheney, for more content like this and other interesting stuff you can visit the following youtube channel, github account, blog and twitter feed.
 nornir is a first-class automation framework, so if you are reading this page, you&amp;rsquo;re probably here to learn more. One of the aspects of which sets nornir apart is filtering.
A new how-to guide has been published to the official documentation, walking through a series of use-cases and examples on how to leverage the power and flexibility of nornir filtering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nornir 3 beta</title>
      <link>/2020/06/18/nornir-3-beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/06/18/nornir-3-beta/</guid>
      <description>I am happy to announce that nornir3 is in beta for you to test. The truth is that it&amp;rsquo;s been out already for a while but at this point I am confident it&amp;rsquo;s stable enough to open it to the wider public for testing.
To install nornir beta you will need to execute the following command:
$ pip install --pre &amp;#34;nornir&amp;gt;=3.0.0b0&amp;#34; Don&amp;rsquo;t forget the --pre option as otherwise pip won&amp;rsquo;t let you install it as it&amp;rsquo;s considered a pre-release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial: Combining Nornir with pyATS</title>
      <link>/2020/05/13/tutorial-combining-nornir-with-pyats/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/05/13/tutorial-combining-nornir-with-pyats/</guid>
      <description>This is a guest post by John McGovern (IPvZero), for more content like this and other interesting stuff you can visit the following youtube channel, github account, and twitter feed.
 This tutorial aims to provide a simple use-case for combining Nornir and pyATS together in order to profile your current network configurations and implement desired state - as specified in host variable definition files.
The workflow we will follow in this tutorial will be first to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>how many threads are enough threads?</title>
      <link>/2020/05/01/how-many-threads-are-enough-threads/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/05/01/how-many-threads-are-enough-threads/</guid>
      <description>The other night there was a discussion about python multi-threading on the nornir channel on slack so I decided to do some benchmarks and explain a couple of things. I am by no means an expert on the topic, I mostly know enough to be scared about the topic and to test assumptions to avoid surprises. I am also going to try to simplify things a bit so apologies in advanced if something is slightly inaccurate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nornir Plugins</title>
      <link>/nornir/plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nornir/plugins/</guid>
      <description>Work in progress. See #486 for details.
If you want to list your plugin here open a PR updating this file</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNaaS-NMS</title>
      <link>/2020/03/03/cnaas-nms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/03/03/cnaas-nms/</guid>
      <description>Github Docs
Campus Network-as-a-Service - Network Management System. Software to automate management of a campus network (LAN). This is an open source software developed as part of SUNETs managed service.
Planned features:
 Zero-touch provisioning of switches Automation of common changes for campus LAN Automated procedure for firmware upgrades Multi-vendor support  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stockpiler</title>
      <link>/2020/03/03/stockpiler/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/03/03/stockpiler/</guid>
      <description>Gtihub
Stockpiler gathers network device configurations and stores them in a local Git repository.
Stockpiler utilizes Nornir, Netmiko, and GitPython for a fully self-contained backup solution, and has been tested to function on Linux, MacOS, and Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About TBD</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsoring the project</title>
      <link>/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>Both nornir and gornir are made by the community for the community. To ensure the continuity and success of the project both collaborators and/or sponsors are welcome.
If you want to sponsor the project you can do it either as an individual using github sponsors or via your company by contacting us via email
Companies sponsoring us Individuals sponsoring us Go to github sponsors and don&amp;rsquo;t forget to thank them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/</guid>
      <description>Community Support You can find community-driven support via the following channels:
 On network to code&amp;lsquo;s slack, #nornir channel On github discussions   Premium Support If you need dedicated support, help developing a feature or plugin, designing and/or architecting your solution or anything else you can reach out to us and discuss your needs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>